Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Communications, Records SC0367
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographs, Accession ARCH-1989-271
  - Football - Individuals (Mohrman, Ogle, Ostrander, Pavko) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Football - Individuals (Royce, Jim Smith, Spence) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Football - Individuals (Thurlow, Volmert, Wilson) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Football - Individuals (Weaver, Clark) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Football - Teams 1935, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Football - Teams 1941, 1946, 1948, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Football - Teams 1951, 1957, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Football - Teams undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Football - Team captions without images (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Golf - Individuals Identified (Pete Choate, Ron Luceti, Bob Blackburn, Stu Ledbetter, Alf Burtleson, Steve Smith) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Golf - Individuals (Unidentified) (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
  - Golf - NCAA, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Golf - Teams (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Indian, Carving of (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Officials (Everett D. Barnes, Walter Byers, 1 unidentified) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Olympic Trials, 1960, 1962 (USA-USSR) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Soccer (unidentified, undated) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Hall of Fame (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Rooting Section (1 image, probably 1950s) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Swimming - Individuals (Moore, Robin) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Swimming - Individuals (Carver Nixon, Mike Zeller, John Jurgensen, Jack Howell, Tom Petersen, John Weiser) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Swimming - Individuals (Unidentified) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Swimming - Individuals (women - 2 images, possibly same woman) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Swimming - Teams & groups (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Tennis - Individuals & duos (all unidentified except for Yoshi Minegishi) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Tennis - Teams (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Track, pre-1950 - Competition Shots (meets) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Track, pre-1950 - Individuals identified (Jim Reynolds, Bob & Gay Bryan, Clyde Jeffry, Bill Miller, Eric Krenz) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Track, pre-1950 - Individuals identified (Bill Eastman & teammates) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Track, pre-1950 - Individuals (unidentified) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Track, - Individuals A-G (D. Fletcher, D. Chesarek, M. Graves, J. Bugge, K. Brownsberger, P. Fehlen, J. Groat, W. Garrett, B. Flint, G. Bryan, B. Bryan, N. Fishback), 1948-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Track, - Individuals J-N (N. Jiles, M. Johnson, R. Love, F. Peters, W. King, B. Lundh, B. Kimball, D. Merchant, J. Luttrell, B. Nelson, K. Nieland, L. Kelley), 1948-1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Track, 1948-1960 - Individuals R-W (B. Stoecker, C. Smart, B. Rupp, J. Stewart, K. Wallace, J. Woollett, J. Saras, B. Reed, B. Simon, C. Strong, H. Roldan, D. Richardson) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Track, - Individuals (unidentified [1]), 1948-1960 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Track, - Individuals (A-G) (J. Goode, G. Porter, S. Cortright, K. Emanuels, D. Deubner, D. Barkley, C. Barth, E. Cunliffe), post-1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Track, - Individuals (K-M) (D. Lassen, D. Martin, J. Kelly, P. Morrison, R. Klier, D. Moore), post-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Track, - Individuals (P-Q) (N. Pease, G. Porter, L. Questad), post-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Track, - Individuals (S-W) (T. Wilkins, C. Smith, B. Stoecker, post-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Track, - Individuals (unidentified), post-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Track, - 1966 mile relay team, post-1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Track, General - Individuals (A-Z) (P. White, J. Weiershauser, S. Klopolock, N. Lloyd, J. Kelly, B. Deacon, F. Herrmann, P. Fehlen, G. Brock, T. Colby) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Track, General - Individuals (unidentified) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Track, General - 1965- 440 relay team (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Track teams (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Trophies & awards, presentation of (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Wilbur, R.L. & Maloney, Harry (1941) (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Additional Records, 1986-1987; Accession ARCH-1990-078
  - Men's Basketball vs Norwegian National 11/16/1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball vs Georgia Tech - Central Fidelity classic, 11/28/1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball vs Rice - Central Fidelity Classis, 11/29/1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball vs San Jose State 12/2/1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball vs St. mary's 12/13/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball vs Oregon 12/21/1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball vs W. Wahington 12/27/1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: Palm Beach Classic, 12/29-12/30/1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball vs Oregon State 12/23/1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball vs UCLA 1/2/1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball vs USC 1/5/1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball vs Washington 1/8/1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball vs Washington State 1/12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball vs Cal 1/17/1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball vs Arizona 1/19/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball vs Arizona State 1/22/1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball vs Oregon State 1/29/1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball vs Oregon 2/1/1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball vs UCLA 2/5/1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball vs USC 2/8/1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball vs Washington State 2/12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball vs Univ. of Washington 2/14/1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball vs Cal 2/22/1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball vs Arizona 2/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball vs Arizona State 2/28/1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball: 1987 Pac 10 Tournament, 3/5 - 3/8/1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/20/1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football vs Oregon State 9/27/1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football vs San Diego State 10/4/1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football vs Washington 10/11/1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football vs Oregon 10/18/1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Football vs USC 10/25/1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Football vs Washington State 11/1/1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Football vs UCLA 11/8/1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Football vs Cal 11/22/1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Football vs Arizona (Coca-Cola Bowl, Tokyo, Japan) 11/29/1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Additional Records, 1984-1988; Accession ARCH-1991-076
  - Football vs. Washington 9/5/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football at Colorado 9/19/1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. San Jose State 9/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. UCLA 10/3/1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football at Washington State 10/10/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football at San Diego State 10/17/1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. Oregon 10/24/1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Arizona 10/31/1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football at USC 11/7/1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football at Oregon State 11/14/1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Football vs. California 11/21/1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Men's basketball vs. Columbia and U.A.B. 1986 (Stanford Apple Invitational) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Men's basketball vs. Malbus 11/15/1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Men's basketball vs. Iowa 11/27/1987 (Maui Classic) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's basketball vs. Chaminade 11/28/1987 (Maui Classic) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's basketball vs. Baylor 11/29/1987 (Maui Classic) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's basketball vs. Santa Clara 12/1/1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's basketball vs. William & Mary 12/3/1987 (Apple Invitational) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Men's basketball vs. Brown 12/5/1987 (Apple Invitational) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Men's basketball vs. USF 12/12/1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Men's basketball vs. Harvard 12/18/1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Men's basketball vs. USC 12/21/1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Men's basketball vs. UCLA 12/23/1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Men's basketball at Hoosier Classic 12/29/1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Men's basketball vs. Seattle Pacific 1/2/88 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Men's basketball vs. Arizona State 1/7/88 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Men's basketball vs. Arizona 1/9/88 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Men's basketball vs. Washington 1/14/88 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Men's basketball vs. Washington State 1/15/88 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball vs. Cal 1/23/88 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Men's basketball vs. Oregon State 1/28/88 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Men's basketball vs. Oregon 1/30/88 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Men's basketball vs. Arizona 2/4/88 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Men's basketball vs. Arizona State 2/6/88 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Men's basketball vs. Washington State2/11/88 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Men's basketball vs. Washington 2/13/88 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Men's basketball vs. Cal 2/21/88 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Men's basketball vs. Oregon 2/25/88 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Men's basketball vs. Oregon State 2/27/88 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Men's basketball vs. UCLA 3/3/88 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Men's basketball vs. USC 3/5/88 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Men's basketball at Pac-10 tourney at Arizona 3/10/88 - 3/13/88 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Men's basketball vs. Long Beach State (NIT) 3/18/88 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Men's basketball vs. Arkansas State (NIT) 3/22/88 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Men's basketball vs. Indiana (NIT) 11/20/88 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Slides of basketball players, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 7/4/1984 - 11/5/1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 11/12/1984 - 2/11/85 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 2/14/85 - 4/8/85 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 4/9/85 - 7/10/85 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 1/5/1986 - 9/29/1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 9/29/1986 - 11/20/1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Sports Information Press Releases, 11/24/1986 - 1/27/1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Football stats (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, June 1984 - October 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, November 1984 - February 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, March 1985 - December 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, January 1986 - September 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, October 1986 - December 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, January 1987 - September 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pac-10 Newsletter, October 1987 - February, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Five binders containing clippings of sports events, 1984 - 1987 (Box 6)
- Additional Records, 1926-1933; Accession ARCH-1991-137
  - Photo Album, 1929-1933: subjects include baseball, football, track, water polo, swimming, boxing, tennis, polo, golf, and basketball teams, usually with their coaches; the Stanford Band; and students with Herbert and Lou Henry Hoover in front of their campus home. (Box 1)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 1 1926-1927 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 2 1927-1928 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 3 1928 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 4 1928-1929 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 5 1929 April - November (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 6 1929 November - December (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 7 1929 December - 1930 April; includes clippings on reclaiming the Ax (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 8 1930 May - 1931 May; including clippings on 1930 Commencement (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 9 1931 September - December; including clippings on the bonfire (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings (news coverage, illustrations, cartoons), tickets and passes: V. 10 1932-1933 (Box 3)
- Additional Records, 1988-1989; Accession ARCH-1991-175
  - Football vs. USC 9/10/88 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. San Diego State 9/17/88 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Oregon 9/24/88 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. Notre Dame 10/1/88 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. San Jose State 10/8/88 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football vs. Arizona State 10/15/88 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football vs. Oregon State 10/22/88 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. Washington 10/29/88 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Washington State 11/5/88 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. UCLA 11/12/88 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. California 11/19/88 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Men's basketball games, 11/18/88 thru 1/16/89 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Men's basketball games, 1/19/89 thru 3/16/89 (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Additional Records, 1985-1990; Accession ARCH-1992-145
  - Press releases, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Press releases, 1987-88 (Box 1)
  - Press releases, 1988-89 (Box 1)
  - Press releases, 1989-90 (Box 1)
  - Baseball [clippings], 1988 (Box 2)
  - Baseball [clippings], 1989 (Box 2)
  - Baseball [clippings], 1990 (Box 2)
  - Basketball [clippings] 1987-88 (Box 2)
  - Basketball [clippings] 1987-88 Book II (Box 3)
  - Men's Basketball [clippings] 1989-90 (Box 3)
  - Pac-10 football releases, 1988, and basketball releases, 1988-89 (Box 3)
  - Football [clippings] 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Football [clippings], 1988 (Box 4)
  - Football [clippings] 1988-89 (Box 4)
  - Football [clippings], 1989 (Box 4)
  - Annual stats (Box 4)
  - Sport clips - women's basketball thru swimming, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Sport clips - tennis thru wrestling, 1987-88 (Box 5)
  - Sport clips - women's basketball thru wrestling, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Press clippings 1988-89 - women's basketball thru men's and women's swimming (Box 6)
  - Press clippings 1988-89 - men's and women's tennis thru wrestling (Box 6)
  - Stanford sports 1989-90 - crew to swimming (Box 6)
  - Stanford sports 1989-90 - tennis to wrestling (Box 7)
- Additional Records, 1989-1990; Accession ARCH-1993-129
  - Football at Arizona 9/2/89 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football at Oregon State 9/9/89 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Oregon 9/23/89 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. San Jose State 9/30/89 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. Notre Dame 10/7/89 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football at Washington State 10/14/89 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football vs. Utah 10/21/89 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Football at USC 10/28/89 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Football vs. UCLA 11/4/89 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football at Arizona Sate 11/11/89 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football vs.Cal 11/18/89 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Football at CAL, 11/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Football at Arizona, 11/10/1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Football vs. Washington St., 11/3/1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Football at Oregon, 10/27/1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Football vs. Washington, 10/20/1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Football vs. USC, 10/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Football vs. Notre Dame, 10/6/1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Football vs. San Jose State, 9/29/1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Football vs. Oregon State, 9/22/1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Football at UCLA, 9/16/1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Football at Colorado, 9/6/1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Women's Basketball Season, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 12-39)
  - Stanford Men's Basketball Season, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 40-68)
- Additional Records, 1967-1993; Accession ARCH-1994-001
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: football 1991; men's and women's various sports 1990-91; women's basketball 1989-90 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: women's basketball 1990-91; baseball 1991; crew to swimming 1991-92 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: tennis to wrestling 1991-92; tennis to water polo 1991; men's basketball 1990-91 (Box 3)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: all sports 1992-93; basketball (men's and women's) 1992-93 (Box 4)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: football 1990; baseball, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Boxing awards memoranda, 1940-69 (Box 5)
  - Two albums of photographs of football, 1986 and undated (Box 5)
  - Loose photographs of football (Box 5)
  - Slides of football players and coaches 1972-74, 1976-79, 1981-82, 1984-1986, 1989-90 (Box 6)
  - Football video tapes: Big Game 1974, 1976; 1977 and 1978 games; Rose Bowl 1971 (Box 7)
  - Football video tapes: 1979 highlights [3/4 in cassette] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs. Boston College, 9/29/79 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs. UCLA 10/6/79 [3/4 in cassette] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs. USC 10/13/79 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs. Arizona 10/20/79 [3/4 in cassette] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs. Arizona State 11/3/79 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs. Arizona State 11/3/79 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: "Post Season" 1979 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: "A Team for the 80's" film to tape transfer (1979 highlights) [3/4 in cassette] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: Stanford at Oregon 9/7/80 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: Stanford at UCLA 10/11/80 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs Washington 10/19/80 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs Oregon State 11/1/80 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: SU vs USC 11/8/80 [U-matic] (Box 8)
  - Football video tapes: 1981, 1982 and 1983 games [possibly as highlights]; 1984 Previews and Highlights (Box 9)
  - Football video tapes: games 9/8/1984 to 11/3/1984 (reels 1-2) (Box 10)
  - Football video tapes: games 11/3/1984 (reels 3-8) to 1985 Key Players (Box 11)
  - Football video tapes: 1985 previews and games; Senior Tribute 5/7/1986; 1986 PAC 10 Preview (Box 12)
  - Football video tapes: 1986 Key Players, Highlights, Recruiting Films and games 9/13/1986 to 11/9/1986 (Box 13)
  - Football video tapes: 11/23/1986 Big Game; 12/27/1986 Gator Bowl; 1987 Senior Tribute (Box 14)
  - Football video tapes: 1987 Previews, Key Players, Coach Jack Elway bites, and games 10/3/1987 to 11/7/1987 (Box 15)
  - Football video tapes: 1988 Previews, Jack Elway interview, and games (Box 16)
  - Football video tapes: 1989 Preview and games with Oregon and Arizona State; 1990 Previews and games 9/15/1990 to 10/13/1990 (Box 17)
  - Football video tapes: 10/20/1990 game; 1991 PAC 10 Highlights; 9/17/1991 game; and footage from ceremony retiring Jim Plunketts' jersey (Box 18)
  - Football video tapes: 1991 games (9/14 to 11/23/1991) (Box 19)
  - Football video tapes: 1992 games; Dennis Green's video resume and file tape; Stanford recruiting tapes; and campus promo spots 1980-84 and undated (Box 20)
  - Football video tapes: campus promo spot 1990 and for East-West game, n.d.; and misc. tapes, Undated (Box 21)
  - Video tapes: misc. football (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: swimming championships, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: women's volleyball, 12/19/88 and 11/30/89 (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: volleyball 11/16/1991 (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: women's soccer 10/14/1991 (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: "3 Meets 1969" and "A Pool's Paradise" by 44 Blue Productions (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: undated tape on Stanford stadium (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: "The Stanford Experience" (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: promo spot "Stanford Academics/ Athletics" Feb., 1990 (Box 22)
  - Video tapes: women's gymnastics, Undated (Box 23)
  - Video tapes: Dick Gould, men's tennis coach, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Video tapes: 1988 College World Series; 1987 College World Series; Stanford baseball vs Cal Fullerton, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Video tapes: interviews with Tara Vanderveer and Mike Montgomery, 1988-89 (Box 23)
  - Video tapes: Pac 10 Women's Programs, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Video tapes: Kodak All-Americans Jennifer Azzi and Trisha Stevens, 1990 (Box 24)
  - Video tapes: promo spote for 1990 NCAA West Regional Women's Championship (Box 24)
  - Video tapes: women's basketball Pac 10 Preview 1987/88, 1988/89, and 1989/1990; Stanford games 1/17/1987, 1/30/1987 11/25/88 and 1/111/1990 (Box 24)
  - Video tapes: women's basketball vs Geo Washington, 11/30/1991 and vs Oregon, Undated (Box 25)
  - Video tapes: men's basketball 1980 feature; 1984 games (Box 25)
  - Video tapes: men's basketball 1985 games; 1986 games; 1987/88 Preview Pac 10 Conference; Cal vs Stanford 2/22/1987 (Box 26)
  - Video tapes: men's basketball 1987 games with Arizona and Arizona State; vs ASU 1/25/88; vs Oregon State 1/5/89; 1990 Pac 10 quarterfinals; 1991 games; vs UCLA 1/25/1992; vs Arizona State 2/8/1992 (Box 27)
  - Video tapes: men's basketball vs Washington State 3/1/1992; 1992/1993 Pac 10 Men's Preview; three misc. tapes (Box 28)
  - 16 mm films: Stanford vs SJSU football 9/19/70; 1971 Rose Bowl; 1985 Stanford Recruiting highlight film (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous plaques of awards to students (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous plaques of awards to students (Box 29)
- Clippings, 1982-1985; Accession ARCH-1994-146
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: baseball 1985, football 1984-85, basketball 1984/85, and fall sports 1982/1983 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on: football 1983-84 and 1984-85, misc. sports 1983-85, and golf 1982-83 (Box 2)
- Additional Records, 1970-1995; Accession ARCH-1995-170
  - Football clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Bill Walsh clippings, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Clippings on Men and Women's Basketball 1991-92 (Box 2)
  - Clippings on Baseball, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Men's Basketball STANFORD INVITATIONAL 11/23-24/1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball Apple Invite 11/30-12/1/1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Santa Clara 12/15/1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball vs. UC Irvine 12/19/1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Florida 12/21/1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball at Colorado 12/23/1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball at Florida Citrus Bowl 12/29-30/1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball at Oregon State 1/3/1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball at Oregon 1/6/1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball vs. WSU 1/12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball at UCLA 1/16/1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball at USC 1/20/1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball vs.Arizona 1/24/1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball vs. ASU 1/27/1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Oregon 1/31/1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Oregon State 2/2/1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball at Washington State 2/7/1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball at Washington 2/10/1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball vs. USC 2/14/1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball vs. UCLA 2/16/1991 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball at Arizona State 2/21/1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Arizona 2/23/1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball vs. CAL 3/2/1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball at CAL 3/7/1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball NIT vs. Houston at Stanford 3/13/1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball NIT at Wisconsin 3/18/1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Men's Basketball NIT game vs. SIU 3/21/1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Men's Basketball NIT games 1991 Champion vs. Oklahoma 3/27/1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Men's Basketball vs. High 5 11/6/1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Brandt Hagen 11/16/1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball Apple Invite 11/22-23/1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Colorado 11/30/1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball at Santa Clara 12/14/1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Virginia 12/21/1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball at Spartan Classic 12/27-28/1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)